A Guide to the Correspondence and subject files of the Director of the Virginia Dept. of Conservation and Recreation, 1958-1989, 1996-2013.
Library of Virginia
- Correspondence and subject files, 1958-1980 (Accession 31845)., Extent: 67 cubic feet (67 boxes)
  - Mineral Resources, Division of
    - Outer Continental Shelf, 1974-1975. (Box 22)
    - Quarterly Reports, 1974-1975. (Box 22)
    - Cave Conservation Committee, 1974-1976. (Box 22)
    - General correspondence and information, 1975-1976. (Box 22)
    - Offshore Exploration and Development, 1975-1976. (Box 22)
    - Outer Continental Shelf, 1975-1976. (Box 22)
    - Quarterly Reports, 1975-1976. (Box 22)
    - Cave Conservation Committee, 1976-1977. (Box 22)
    - General correspondence and information, 1976-1977. (Box 22)
    - Outer Continental Shelf, 1976-1977. (Box 22)
    - quarterly Reports, 1976-1977. (Box 22)
    - General correspondence and information, 1977-1978. (Box 22)
    - Quarterly Reports, 1977-1978. (Box 22)
    - General correspondence and information, 1978-1979. (Box 22)
    - Quarterly Reports, 1978-1979. (Box 22)
    - Topographic Mapping Program, 1962-1979. (Box 22)
    - General correspondence and information, 1979-1980. (Box 22)
    - Outer Continental Shelf, 1979-1980. (Box 22)
    - Quarterly Reports, 1979-1980. (Box 22)
    - Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University - Cost Reimbursement Subcontract, 1979-1980. (Box 22)
  - State Parks, Division of
    - National Youth Corps, 1965-1966. (Box 23)
    - Acquisition and Development Program, 1966-1967. (Box 23)
    - Revenue Bonds, 1963-1971. (Box 23)
    - General correspondence and information, 1974-1975. (Box 23)
    - Quarterly Reports, 1974-1975. (Box 23)
    - General correspondence and information, 1975-1976. (Box 23)
    - Park Bond Issue, 1973-1976. (Box 23)
    - Quarterly Reports, 1975-1976. (Box 23)
    - Parks - Rules and Regulations, 1971-1976. (Box 23)
    - General correspondence and information, 1976-1977. (Box 23)
    - Quarterly Reports, 1976-1977. (Box 23)
    - General correspondence and information, 1977-1978. (Box 23)
    - Quarterly Reports, 1977-1978. (Box 23)
    - Camp Pendleton proposed land transfer, 1978-1979. (Box 23)
    - Chippokes Farm Foundation, 1978-1979. (Box 23)
    - Conservators of the Peace, 1978-1979. (Box 23)
    - General correspondence and information, 1978-1979. (Box 23)
    - Quarterly Reports, 1978-1979. (Box 23)
    - Chippokes Farm Foundation, 1979-1980. (Box 23)
    - Conservators of the Peace, 1979-1980. (Box 23)
    - General correspondence and information, 1979-1980. (Box 23)
    - Quarterly Reports, 1979-1980. (Box 23)
    - Tranfer Agreement - Parks to Game Commission - Pea Hill Boat Landing, 1979-1980. (Box 23)
    - Youth Conservation Corps, 1977-1980. (Box 23)
    - Appalachian Trail, 1970-1979. (Box 24)
    - Bear Creek Lake State Park, 1977-1978. (Box 24)
    - Bull Run Mountain State Park, 1972-1979. (Box 24)
    - Caledon State Park, 1973-1979. (Box 24)
    - Chippokes Plantation acquisition, 1957-1974. (Box 24)
    - Chippokes Plantation State Park, 1967-1980. (Box 24)
    - Chippokes Model Farm Foundation, 1974-1979. (Box 24)
    - Claytor Lake State Park, 1966-1979. (Box 24)
    - Dismal Swamp - Cooperative Forest Fire Agreement, 1973-1979. (Box 24)
    - Dismal Swamp - Corps of Engineers correspondence, 1969-1976. (Box 24)
    - Dismal Swamp - Alvah Duke correspondence, 1967-1973. (Box 24)
    - Dismal Swamp, 1954-1970. (Box 24)
    - Dismal Swamp, 1970-1971. (Box 24)
    - Dismal Swamp, 1972-1973. (Box 25)
    - Dismal Swamp, 1973-1974. (Box 25)
    - Dismal Swamp, 1974-1977. (Box 25)
    - Fairy Stone State Park, 1967-1968. (Box 25)
    - False Cape State Park, 1966-1973. (Box 25)
    - False Cape State Park, 1974-1975. (Box 25)
    - False Cape State Park, 1976-1980. (Box 25)
    - Fort Boykin, 1963-1976. (Box 25)
    - Fort Story - Housing controversy, 1974-1977. (Box 25)
    - Goshen Pass, 1967-1975. (Box 25)
    - Grayson Highlands State Park, 1963-1978. (Box 25)
    - Hungry Mother State Park, 1969-1979. (Box 25)
    - Lake Anna State Park, 1972-1976. (Box 26)
    - Leesylvania State Park, 1977-1980. (Box 26)
    - Mason Neck State Park, 1965-1975. (Box 26)
    - Natural Bridge properties, 1974-1976. (Box 26)
    - Natural Tunnel, 1966-1967. (Box 26)
    - Occoneechee State Park, 1976-1977. (Box 26)
    - Pocahontas State Park, 1967-1980. (Box 26)
    - Rosewell, 1962-1967. (Box 26)
    - Sayler's Creek Battlefield, 1969-1970. (Box 26)
    - Seashore State Park, 1963-1978. (Box 26)
    - Smith Mountain Lake State Park, 1963-1979. (Box 26)
    - Southwest Virginia Museum, 1964-1965. (Box 26)
    - George Washington National Parkway, 1965-1979. (Box 26)
    - Westmoreland State Park, 1966-1978. (Box 26)
    - Wiggington's Island, 1962-1963. (Box 26)
    - York River State Park, 1967-1980. (Box 26)
  - Virginia State Travel Service (VSTS)
    - Advertising account prequalification questionnaires, 1974. (Box 27)
    - Information Stations (I-81 and I-64) - correspondence to CHH DEF and Dept., 1968. (Box 27)
    - Information Stations - History, 1971-1972. (Box 27)
    - Information Stations - Survey (Interstate Highways), 1964. (Box 27)
    - Information Stations, 1958-1967. (Box 27)
    - Information Stations, 1967 July-Dec. (Box 27)
    - Information Stations, 1968 Jan-Mar. (Box 27)
    - Information Stations, 1968 Apr-June. (Box 27)
    - Information Stations, 1968-1969. (Box 27)
    - Information Stations, 1970-1971. (Box 27)
    - Information Stations, 1971-1972. (Box 27)
    - Information Stations, 1972-1973. (Box 27)
    - Information Stations, 1973-1974. (Box 27)
    - Bicentennial Commission, 1973-1974. (Box 27)
    - Southeastern Institute of Research, 1968-1969. (Box 27)
    - Advertising Agency, 1974-1975. (Box 28)
    - Bicentennial Commission, 1974-1975. (Box 28)
    - General correspondence and information, 1974-1975. (Box 28)
    - Information Stations, 1974-1975. (Box 28)
    - Inquiries, Report of, 1974-1975. (Box 28)
    - News Releases and Clipbook, 1974-1975. (Box 28)
    - Quarterly Reports, 1974-1975. (Box 28)
    - Southern Travel Directors Council, 1974-1975. (Box 28)
    - State Chamber Travel Reception - New York, 1974 Nov 6. (Box 28)
    - Travel Advisory Committee, 1974-1975. (Box 28)
    - Travel Coordinating Committee, 1974-1975. (Box 28)
    - Travelog, 1974-1975. (Box 28)
    - Weekly Staff Meetings, 1974-1975. (Box 28)
    - Advertising Agency, 1975-1976. (Box 28)
    - Bicentennial Commission, 1975-1976. (Box 28)
    - Bicentennial Commission - Advertising, 1975-1976. (Box 28)
    - General correspondence and information, 1975-1976. (Box 28)
    - Information Stations, 1975-1976. (Box 28)
    - Inquiries, Report of, 1975-1976. (Box 28)
    - News Releases and Clipbook, 1975-1976. (Box 28)
    - Quarterly Reports, 1975-1976. (Box 28)
    - Travel Advisory Committee, 1975-1976. (Box 28)
    - Travelog, 1975-1976. (Box 28)
    - Weekly Staff Meetings, 1975-1976. (Box 28)
    - Arts and Humanities, Virginia Commission for the, 1970-1977. (Box 28)
    - Bicentennial Commission, 1976-1977. (Box 28)
    - Advertising Agency - Communication, 1975-1977. (Box 28)
    - General correspondence and information, 1976-1977. (Box 28)
    - Information Stations, 1976-1977. (Box 28)
    - Information Stations - Proposed for US 23 - VA 630, 1975-1976. (Box 28)
    - Inquiries, Report of, 1976-1977. (Box 28)
    - News Releases and Clipbook, 1976-1977. (Box 28)
    - Quarterly Reports, 1976-1977. (Box 28)
    - Travel Film - Colony Productions, 1975-1977. (Box 28)
    - Travelog, 1976-1977. (Box 28)
    - Weekly Staff Meetings, 1976-1977. (Box 28)
    - Bicentennial Commission, 1977-1978. (Box 29)
    - General correspondence and information, 1977-1978. (Box 29)
    - Information Stations, 1977-1978. (Box 29)
    - Information Stations - New Kent County, proposed, 1977-1978. (Box 29)
    - Inquiries, Report of, 1977-1978. (Box 29)
    - New Releases, 1977-1978. (Box 29)
    - Quarterly Reports, 1977-1978. (Box 29)
    - Canadian Advertising Grant, 1974-1979. (Box 29)
    - Advertising Agency - Hearings, 1978-1979. (Box 29)
    - DeBolt Contract, 1978-1979. (Box 29)
    - General correspondence and information, 1978-1979. (Box 29)
    - Information Stations, 1978-1979. (Box 29)
    - Inquiries, Report of, 1978-1979. (Box 29)
    - Quarterly Reports, 1978-1979. (Box 29)
    - Gasoline information, 1979-1980. (Box 29)
    - General correspondence and information, 1979-1980. (Box 29)
    - Proposed Governor's Travel Conference, 1979-1980. (Box 29)
    - Information Stations, 1979-1980. (Box 29)
    - Inquries, Reports of, 1979-1980. (Box 29)
    - Quarterly Reports, 1979-1980. (Box 29)
    - Travel Statistics, 1979-1980. (Box 29)
  - Boards and Commissions
    - Cave Commission, 1977-1980. (Box 30)
    - Cave Commission - Cave sign, 1979-1980. (Box 30)